Register of the Dixy Lee Ray papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- GOVERNORSHIP, 1977-1981
  - Speeches (arranged alphabetically by name of requesting group or occasion). See also State of the state addresses
    - United Association, Spokane, Washington, 25 April 1980
    - United for Washington, Tacoma, Washington, 29 March 1979
    - United Inner-City Foundation, Seattle, Washington, 30 January 1980
    - United Steelworkers of America, District 38, Spokane, Washington, 14 June 1978
    - United Way-Kitsap County, Bremerton, Washington, 24 March 1980
    - University District Kiwanis Club, Seattle, Washington, 25 August 1980
    - University of Puget Sound, Tacoma, Washington, 16 September 1980
    - University of Washington, Seattle, Washington
      - Commencement, 10 June 1978
      - Insitute on Aging, 24 May 1979
      - Reserve Officers Training Corps Review (Governor's Day and Tri-Service Review)
        - 12, May 1978
        - 18, May 1979
        - 16, May 1980
    - Valley Council of the Spokane Board of Realtors, Spokane, Washington, 14 May 1980
    - Valley Senior Center, Spokane, Washington, 20 April 1979
    - Vernie Reed banquet, Olympia, Washington, 18 January 1980
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars
      - New Orleans, Louisiana, 20 August 1979
      - Everett, Washington, 20 June 1980
    - Warren G. Magnuson Health Sciences Center, Seattle, Washington, 3 November 1978
    - Warren G. Magnuson Intercollegiate Nursing Building, Spokane, Washington, 27 August 1980
    - Washington Apartment Association, Spokane, 7 September 1979
    - Washington Association of Broadcasters, Seattle, 10 March 1980
    - Washington Association of Conservation Districts, Spokane
      - 26 November 1979
      - 17, January 1980
    - Washington Association of Sheriffs and Police Chiefs, Richland, 19 June 1980
    - Washington Association of Wheat Growers, Spokane, 3 December 1978
    - "Washington Award for 1978," Chicago, Illinois, 22 February 1978
    - Washington Bond Club, Seattle, 7 August 1980
    - Washington Cattlemen's Association, Spokane, 8 November 1979
    - Washington Contract Loggers Association, Olympia (Box 156)
      - 16, March 1979
      - 14, March 1980
    - Washington Council on International Trade, Seattle, 21, August 1980
    - Washington Federation of State Employees, AFL-CIO, Spokane, 30 September 1978
    - Washington Hearing Aid Society, Seattle, 30 June 1979
    - Washington Hispanic-American Society, Olympia, 14 April 1979
    - Washington Home Builders Association, Seattle, 30 April 1979
    - Washington Housing Forum, Tacoma, 30 September 1978
    - Washington Immigration Action Committee, Olympia, 28 February 1980
    - Washington Independence Telephone Association, Seattle, 27 June 1979
    - Washington Newspaper Publishers Association
      - Spokane, 21, September 1978
      - Tumwater, 15 February 1979
    - Washington-Oregon Shippers Cooperative Association, Seattle, 7 April 1978
    - Washington-Oregon Soft Drink Association, Seattle, 1 May 1979
    - Washington Personnel Management Association, Olympia, (delivered by David Jenkins), 2 May 1978
    - Washington Precast Concrete Industry, Seattle, 26 June 1980
    - Washington Public Power Supply System, Olympia, 19 October 1979
    - Washington Pulp and Paper Foundation, Seattle, 18 October 1979
    - Washington State Apprenticeship and Training Council, Olympia, 17 July 1980
    - Washington State Association of Counties
      - Olympia, 28 June 1978
      - Spokane, 29 June 1979
      - Union, 17 January 1980
      - Ocean Shores, 27 June 1980
    - Washington State Association of County Assessors, Yakima, 12 September 1979
    - Washington State Association of Fire Chiefs, Wenatchee, 25 June 1979
    - Washington State Builders, Seattle, 30 April 1979
    - Washington State Building and Construction Trades Council
      - Spokane, (delivered by Paul Bender), 10 August 1978
      - Seattle, 16 August 1979
    - Washington State Cable Television Association, Olympia, 21, February 1979
    - Washington State Conference for People with Disabilities, Olympia, (delivered by Paul Bender), 10 November 1978
    - Washington State Convention of the American G.I. Forum, Olympia, 3 June 1978
    - Washington State Council of Carpenters (Box 157)
      - Pasco, 13 April 1978
      - Moscow, Idaho, 10 April 1980
    - Washington State Council of Culinary Workers, Bartenders and Hotel Service Employees, Tacoma, 7 September 1979
    - Washington State County Clerks Association, Ocean Shores, 6 August 1980
    - Washington State Credit Union, Olympia, 12 September 1980
    - Washington State Democratic Committee
      - Spokane, 1 July 1978
      - Olympia, 27 January 1979
      - Hoquiam, 14 June 1980
    - Washington State Democratic Party
      - 11th District, location unknown, 16 September 1978
      - 29th District, Tacoma, 2 September 1980
    - Washington State Departments. See Speeches, Departments
    - Washington State Energy Council, Seattle
      - 11 December 1978
      - 28 August 1979
    - Washington State Farm Bureau, Olympia, 13 February 1980
    - Washington State Funeral Directors, Seattle, 9 June 1980
    - Washington State Grange
      - Bellingham, 19 June 1978
      - Pullman, 23 June 1980
    - Washington State Hospital Association, Spokane, 7 October 1978
    - Washington State Labor Council, AFL-CIO
      - Spokane, 31, August 1978
      - Seattle, 26 August 1980
    - Washington State Medical Association, Seattle, 6 October 1979
    - Washington State Patrol, Olympia
      - 28 June 1979
      - 30 June 1980
    - Washington State Pharmaceutical Association, Seattle, 25 June 1978
    - Washington State Trade and Convention Center, Seattle, 4 December 1978
    - Washington State Transportation Conference, Seattle, 10 September 1980
    - West Seattle Chamber of Commerce, West Seattle, Washington, 9 February 1979 (Box 158)
    - Western Association of Graduate Schools, Seattle, Washington, 2 March 1980
    - Western Conference, The Council of State Govern- ments, Spokane, Washington, 14 August 1978
    - Western Conference of Independent Telephone Companies, Seattle, Washington, 27 June 1979
    - Western Conference of Public Service Commissions, Seattle, Washington, 13 June 1979
    - Western Conference of Teamsters, Seattle, Washington, 27 August 1979
    - Western Environmental Trade Association, Tumwater, Washington, 2 November 1978
    - Western States Liquor Administrators, Seattle, Washington, 7 September 1978
    - Western States Restaurant and Hotel Convention, Seattle, Washington, 13 June 1978
    - Western Washington Horticultural Society, Olympia, Washington, 9 January 1980
    - Weyerhaeuser Corporation
      - Informal meeting, Olympia, Washington, 9 November 1977
      - Technology Center dedication, Federal Way, Washington, 26 September 1978
    - Whatcom County Development Council, 14 February 1979
    - White House Council on Wage Price Stability, Seattle, Washington, 12 April 1979
    - Women's Business Exchange, Seattle, Washington, 15 May 1980
    - Women's Political Caucus, Olympia, Washington, 11 November 1979
    - World Trade Council, Seattle, Washington, 21, August 1980
    - Yakima Capitol Theatre dedication, Yakima, Washington, 4 November 1978
    - Yakima County Democratic Convention, Yakima, Washington, 6 May 1978
    - Yakima County 4-H Recognition banquet, Yakima, Washington, 10 November 1979
    - Yakima County Retired Teachers Association, Yakima, Washington, 21, June 1978
    - Yakima Indian Tribal Meeting on Water Rights, Topenish, Washington, 23 March 1979
    - Yakima Rotary and Kiwanis Clubs, Yakima, Washington, 19 July 1979
    - YMCA Youth Legislature, Olympia, Washington
      - 11 April 1978
      - 19 April 1979
  - State of the state address to a joint session of the Washington State Legislature
    - 16, January 1979
    - 15, January 1980
  - Statement on the state of the economy in Washington, 29 September 1980
  - Task forces and groups (3 folders) (Box 159)
  - Taxes (2 folders)
  - Television appearances
    - General
    - Phil Donahue Show, Correspondence (3 folders), 26 October 1979 (Box 160)
    - Question and answer newscasts following President Carter's speeches on energy, 5 April and 15 July 1979 (5 folders) (Box 161)
    - Reporter's Roundup, 9 July 1978
    - Viewpoint on the News
      - 18, March 1979
      - l, April 1979
  - Testimonies (Box 162)
  - Tolan, Fred H.
  - Town Hall Meetings, State of Washington
    - General
    - Bellevue, 11 September 1980
    - Bremerton, (2 folders), 13 May 1980
    - Walla Walla, 23 May 1978
    - West Seattle, 4 June 1980
    - Willapa Harbor-Raymond, 11 September 1979 (Box 163)
  - Transition - Cooperation with Governor-elect Spellman
  - Travel
    - General
    - United States
    - Far East
      - Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, (2 folders), October 1977
      - Japan, People's Republic of China, (2 folders), September 1979
  - Washington State agencies, boards and commissions (Box 164)
    - Agriculture Department (2 folders)
    - Athletic Commission
    - Attorney General
    - Commerce and Economic Development Department
    - Community College Education Board
    - Ecology Department (2 folders)
    - Emergency Services Department
    - Employment Development Services Council
    - Employment Security Department
    - Energy Facility Site Evaluation Council (Box 165)
    - Energy Office (4 folders)
    - Finance Committee
    - Financial Management Office (Box 166)
    - Fisheries Department (2 folders). See also Indian Affairs Department and SUBJECT FILE, Indian affairs
    - Gambling Commission
    - Game Department
    - General Administration Department (2 folders)
    - Historical Society
    - Indian Affairs Department. See also Fisheries Department (Box 167)
    - Industrial Insurance Appeals Board
    - Labor and Industries Department
    - Licensing Department
    - Liquor Control Board
    - Military Department
    - Natural Resources Department
    - Oceanographic Commission
    - Parks and Recreation Commission
    - Patrol, State
    - Personnel Department
    - Planning and Community Affairs Agency
    - Postsecondary Education Council
    - Postsecondary Education Council (Box 168)
    - Printing Department
    - Prison Terms and Paroles Board
    - Public Instruction, Superintendent of
    - Retirement Systems Department
    - Revenue Department
    - Social and Health Services Department (3 folders)
    - Social and Health Services Department (Box 169)
    - State Employees Insurance Board
    - Supreme Court
    - Tax Appeals Board
    - Traffic Safety Commission
    - Transportation Department (2 folders)
    - Treasurer
    - Urban Arterial Board
    - Utilities and Transportation Commission
    - Veterans Affairs Department
  - Welfare
  - Western Governors' Conference
    - 1977
    - 1979
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS, 1937-1981
  - Awards, certificates, citations (45) (Box 170)
  - Guest books (7) (Box 171)
  - Honorary degrees (22) (Box 172)
  - Miscellanea, including birthday cards, calendars, clippings, commencement programs, invitations, drawings, license plates, office signs (Box 173)
  - Photograph albums of DLR while chairman of the Atomic Energy Commission and governor of the State of Washington (9) (Box 174)
  - Photograph albums of DLR while governor of the State of Washington (8) (Box 175)
  - Photograph album, scrapbooks (2), sister-city relationship certificate albums, including photographs (5) (Box 176)
  - Travel memorabilia from two trips to the Far East in including books, flags, photograph albums, scrapbooks (20 items), 1977 and 1979 (Box 177)
- PHONOTAPE CASSETTES
  - 242 cassettes of speeches and interviews given by DLR while governor of the State of Washington; 3 cassettes of speeches by others at the Pacific Science Center: 2 cassettes of songs composed by individuals (2) (Box 178-180)
- PERSONAL AND CONFIDENTIAL MATERIALS (Box 181)
  - ATOMIC ENERGY COMMISSION
    - Envelope on which Dixy Lee Ray wrote: "These materials should be held confidential - not open to general scrutiny during the lifetime of the subject individual (former AEC Commissioner Clarence Larson)"
    - Handwritten letter/memorandum to DLR from Gom...? on the role of the AEC, relationship with other agencies, etc. PERSONAL
    - Study entitled "An Alternative Energy Strategy," by Conan. CONFIDENTIAL
  - INTERIM YEARS
    - Letter and curriculum vitae of Malvern Gilmartin, Director of the Australian Institute of Science. PERSONAL
    - Memorandum and attachments for members of the Defense Science Board. SECRET
  - GUBERNATORIAL CAMPAIGNS
    - 1976: envelope of materials from John Vernon Kamm, marked PERSONAL AND CONFIDENTIAL
    - -letter to DLR from John Sylvester re "Former Students of Dixy for Governor" marked by DLR "PUT IN PERSONAL CONFIDENTIAL LOCKED FILE", 1980:
    - -memorandum to DLR from Louis Guzzo on Gambling Trial coverage. CONFIDENTAIL, 1980:
  - GOVERNORSHIP
    - Folder labeled "Democratic Platforms" marked DO NOT ARCHIVE, SAVE
    - Folder marked CONFIDENTIAL, PERSONNEL FILES
    - Letter and enclosure to DLR from William Hutchinson, President and Director of Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center. PERSONAL AND CONFIDENTIAL
    - Letter to DLR from Albert Turrill re demand for position in DLR's administration. CONFIDENTIAL
    - Letters to DLR from Fred Tolan re China trip, HOLD PRIVATE meeting with Seattle CONFIDENTIAL, 15-28 September 1979
    - Letter to DLR from Gordon Culp and attachment entitled "Draft Statement for Governor Ray for April ll Northwest Governors' Meeting on Regional Electric Energy Matters." PERSONAL AND CONFIDENTIAL
    - Letter to DLR from Robert Mucklestone and attachment entitled "Estate Plannning Data." CONFIDENTIAL
    - Memorandum (clipped together with "A Summary - Aluminum Industry in Washington State and Possible Energy Shortage Impacts," Jack Wood) to DLR from Bob Mickelson re Task Group on Economic Development and Employment. CONFIDENTIAL
    - Memorandum to DLR from Dean Cole re Section 8 (housing). CONFIDENTIAL
    - Memorandum to DLR from Jack Wood re indications of diesel demand. CONFIDENTIAL
    - Memorandum to DLR from Joe Zaspel re tourism. CONFIDENTIAL
    - Memorandum to DLR from Louis Guzzo re Senator Al Williams' hearings on Historic Preservation. CONFIDENTIAL
    - Memorandum to DLR from R.Y. Woodhouse re Jay Spearman, Chairman and Executive Secretary of the Washington State Barber Examining Board. CONFIDENTIAL, RE PERSONNEL
    - Memorandum to DLR from the Department of Social and Health Services and enclosure re scandal in one of the Seattle offices (statutory rape of the 3rd degree). CONFIDENTIAL
    - Outline of thesis on international trade sent to DLR by Rita? (Burlington Northern). PERSONAL AND CONFIDENTIAL
    - Study entitled "Management Review, Washington State Department of Emergency Services," CONFIDENTIAL, November 1978
    - Study entitled "Management Review, Washington State Energy Office," CONFIDENTIAL, November 1979
    - Vault-lst floor key (in sealed envelope)
- MEMORABILIA.
  - Approximately 100 items and plaques presented to Memorabilia DLR, mostly upon giving lectures while chairman of the Atomic Energy Commission and governor of the State of Washington (Box 182-185)
- MOTION PICTURE FILMS.
  Access Information
  - "Mount St. Helens," Less than 50 ft., 16mm film
  - "Animals of the Seashore #6," 900 ft., 16mm film (Film shelf)
  - "Animals of the Seashore #11," 1100 ft., 16mm film (Film shelf)
  - "Animals of the Seashore #13," 1500 ft., 16mm film (Film shelf)
  - 12 unlabeled 16mm films, 720-1190 ft. each (Film shelf)
- PHONORECORDS.
  - 2 records of songs entitled "Lovely Seattle/Win Some, Lose Some" and "Dixy Lee Ray or They All Want Her Back Again" (Cabinet Record cabinet)
- VIDEOTAPE CASSETTES.
  - l videotape cassette on Mount St. Helens entitled "The Mountain Erupts,", 9 June 1980 (Cabinet Tape cabinet)
- PHOTOGRAPHS., 1863 prints, 12 postcards, 112 negatives, 109 slides / 135 envelopes, 1 oversize box, 7 slide boxes. (Othertype 10.A-V)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at school., 1929 (Folder mA)
  - 35 prints of Dixy Lee Ray., undated (Folder B)
  - 56 prints of portraits of Dixy Lee Ray., undated (Folder C-E)
  - 17 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at commencement ceremonies., undated (Folder F)
  - 7 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with her sisters., undated (Folder G)
  - 40 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with others, on informal occasions., undated (Folder H)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Explorer's Club (Waldorf Astoria) diner for Lowell Thomas., undated (Folder I)
  - 6 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Fox Island., undated (Folder J)
  - 80 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with her dogs., undated (Folder K-N)
  - 12 postcards of India., 1962 (Folder O)
  - 114 prints of the TE VEGA expedition., 1963 (Folder P-Q)
  - 10 prints illustrating various behavioral aspects of ocypode ceratophthalma., undated (Folder R)
  - 102 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the AEC (miscellanea)., undated (Folder S-V)
  - 1 print of an exhibit at the AEC., undated (Folder W)
  - 4 prints of the AEC Christmas party., 1974 (Folder X)
  - 5 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the "last hurrah" reception for the AEC, with Glenn Seaborg and Mrs. Lewis Strauss., December 4, 1974 (Folder Y)
  - 2 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the last meeting of the AEC, with William Anders, Paul C. Bender and William A. Kriegsman., December 31, 1974 (Folder Z)
  - 1 print of Dixy Lee Ray with the Division of Classification Professional Women, AEC., December 17, 1974 (Folder AA)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with the Division of Controlled Thermonuclear Research, AEC, with Robert L. Hirsch., undated (Folder AB)
  - 34 prints of Dixy Lee Ray in Amtchitka, Alaska for the Cannikin Test, Bioenvironmental Program., July 1973 (Folder AC-AD)
  - 1 print of Dixy Lee Ray at the ARCS Foundation Award ceremony, Beverly Hills, Ca., June 22, 1974 (Folder AE)
  - 11 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Argonne National Laboratory Argonne, Ill., November 1, 1972 (Folder AF)
  - 6 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Battelle Institute Richland, VA., undated (Folder AG)
  - 4 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Bendix Corporation, Kansas City, Kansas., August 25, 1972 (Folder AH)
  - 1 print depicting an anti-nuclear protest at the dedication of the Fermi National Accelerator., May 11, 1974 (Folder AI)
  - 9 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Toastmasters Club, Germantown, Maryland., undated (Folder AJ)
  - 21 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Hanford, WA. with Thomas Nemzek and William O. Doub., undated (Folder AK)
  - 6 prints of Dixy Lee Ray in Idaho Falls, Idaho., 1972 (Folder AL)
  - 29 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Nevada Test Site, in Jackass Flats., 1972 (Folder AM-AO)
  - 9 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Los Alamos, NM with Harold Agnew., undated (Folder AP)
  - 2 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at "Meet the Press", April 14, 1974 (Folder AQ)
  - 9 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Mound Laboratory, Dayton Ohio., October 30, 1972 (Folder AR)
  - 6 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at NASA, Washington D.C., 1973 (Folder AS)
  - 2 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Navy War College, Washington D.C., with Admiral M.G. Bayne., October 2, 1973 (Folder AT)
  - 9 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Oak Ridge National Laboratory, Oak Ridge, Tenn., 1972 (Folder AU)
  - 35 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Rio Blanco Site, Colorado and of the anti-nuclear demonstration., undated (Folder AV)
  - 4 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Rocky Flats, Golden, Colorado., undated (Folder AW)
  - 5 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Sandia Laboratories, Albuquerque, NM., August 22, 1972 (Folder AX)
  - 2 prints depicting the solar energy project at the Grover Cleveland Junior High School, Dorchester, Mass., 1974 (Folder AY)
  - 9 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the St. Vrain Plant, Colorado, with William Anders, Wayne Aspinall, Orval Hansen, Craig Hosmer, R.E. Parsons, Art Rolander., undated (Folder AZ)
  - 8 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the UC Lawrence Berkeley Laboratory, Berkeley, CA., undated (Folder BA)
  - 13 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Union Carbide Corporation, Nuclear Division, Paducah, Kentucky., October 20, 1972 (Folder BB)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with the U.S. Coast Guard., undated (Folder BC)
  - 8 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the White House Meeting on Energy with Frederick Dent, Robert Newlin, Morton Rogers., May 16, 1974 (Folder BD)
  - 4 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with Senator Bellman., undated (Folder BE)
  - 6 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with Senator Dominick., undated (Folder BF)
  - 8 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with President Ford., undated (Folder mBG)
  - 9 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with Alexander Haig., undated (Folder BH)
  - 8 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with President Nixon., undated (Folder mBI)
  - 2 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with Nelson Rockefeller and President Nixon., undated (Folder BJ)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with Commissioner James Ramery., undated (Folder BK)
  - 35 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at an AEC reception, with Admiral Rickover., undated (Folder BL)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with ERDA members., undated (Folder BM)
  - 12 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the State Department (misc.), undated (Folder BN)
  - 6 prints depicting Dixy Lee Ray being sworn-in as Assistant Secretary of State with Henry Kissinger., January 29, 1975 (Folder BO)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray's office at the State Department., undated (Folder BP)
  - 7 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with the U.S.-Iran Joint Commission meeting., May 23, 1975 (Folder BQ)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with Henry Kissinger and Nelson Rockefeller., undated (Folder mBR)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at a United Way gathering., September 26, 1975 (Folder BS)
  - 10 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Brookhaven., December 9-10, 1975 (Folder BT)
  - 4 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at the Evergreen Safety Council., October 3, 1975 (Folder BU)
  - 4 prints of Dixy Lee Ray., 1976 (Folder BV)
  - 14 prints relating to the bomb threat scare in Olympia., 1976 (Folder BW)
  - 80 prints depicting Dixy Lee Ray's campaign., 1976 (Folder BX-BZ)
  - 2 prints depicting Dixy Lee Ray voting at Fox Island., November 2, 1976 (Folder CA)
  - 16 prints depicting the election night/victory party at the Tacoma Bicentennial Pavilion., November 2, 1976 (Folder CB)
  - 32 prints depicting Dixy Lee Ray being sworn-in as Governor in Olympia., January 12, 1977 (Folder CC)
  - 10 prints depicting the office party in Dixy Lee Ray's Governor's office on the first day at work, with Louis Guzzo., undated (Folder CD)
  - 24 prints depicting the inaugural balls in Olympia (January 12) and Tacoma (January 25) (Folder CE)
  - 4 prints depicting the inaugural ball at the Elks Club in Port Angeles., January 14, 1976 (Folder CF)
  - 74 prints depicting Dixy Lee Ray's 1980 campaign., undated (Folder CG-CH)
  - 335 prints of Dixy Lee Ray as Governor (miscellanea), undated (Folder CI-CV)
  - 18 prints depicting the Governor's Mansion., undated (Folder CW)
  - 5 prints depicting ships named after Governor Ray., undated (Folder CX)
  - 5 prints of Dixy Lee Ray with Chevron executives., undated (Folder CY)
  - 6 prints depicting Dixy Lee Ray dedicating fisheries., undated (Folder CZ)
  - 4 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Ellensburg rodeo., undated (Folder DA)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at her first press conference., undated (Folder DB)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray flying in the cockpit of a Goodyear plane., undated (Folder DC)
  - 8 prints of Dixy Lee Ray greeting Vice-Premier Deng of the People's Republic of China., 1979 (Folder DD)
  - 3 prints of Dixy Lee Ray greeting Japanese officials., undated (Folder DE)
  - 11 prints depicting Dixy Lee Ray at various horse races., undated (Folder DF)
  - 9 prints depicting Dixy Lee Ray reviewing troops at Keyport., November 9, 1977 (Folder DG)
  - 11 prints of Dixy Lee Ray at Los Alamos., 1978 (Folder DH)
  - 31 prints relating to the eruption of Mount St. Helens., May 1980 (Folder mDI)